Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 1
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 1
- Box: 3, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Caisse de Compensation paritaireConseil d'Administration, 1950; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Contrats Collectifs en Droit Belge, 1950; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Constitution as revised by the Sixth World Congress, 1959; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Travaux du Seminaire de sociologie de la Faculte de droit de Liege, 1951; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Histoire d'un conflit de travail, 1950; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Author: Arthur Doucy
  - Item 9: Les conventions internationales du travail et le syndicalisme, 1953; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: UITP / Union Internationale des Transports Publics International Union of Public Transport Internationaler Verein Fur Offentliches Verkehrswesen, 1959; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Box: 3, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Realisations de la Medicine du Travail dans l'IndustrieVerviers, 1950; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: L'Apprentissage a Mi-Temps dans l'Industrie Textile de Verviers, 1950; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Fonds de Securite d'Existence en faveur desVervietoise, 1950; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Aide a La Famille (Allocations Prenatales & Complement Familial), 1951; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Centrale Generale des Travailleurs du BatimentsDiverses, 1955; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Liste des Publications, 1958; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Caisse de Compensation paritaire26eme Excercice Social, 1950; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Fondement de L'autorite dans l'enterprise, 1950; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Le Chomage Complet au 20 Septembre 1952, Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: Les Conseils d'Enterprise: Legislation - Doctrine - Jurisprudence, 1952; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: L'Institution d'un Ordre des reviseurs d'entreprise, 1950; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: Loi sure le Contrat de Travail / Loi sur le Contrat d'Emploi, 1954; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Item 13: Recensement semestriel des chomeurs complets, 1952; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Box: 3, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Europaische Dokumentation, 1971; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Notes: Conference material
  - Item 2: Congress Press Summary (11th World Congress_), 1975; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Author: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions
  - Item 3: Youngstown Sheet and Tube Company in Belgium, 1961; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Constitution: adopted at the First Congress, 1975; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Box: 3, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Report of the special joint meeting of the ICFTUPurposes Committee, 1969; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Asian Regional Organisation and trade union situationcountries, 1964; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Changing WFTU tactics in devloping countries, 1962; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: European Regional Organisation: Report on Executive Board, 1964; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: WFTU Conference on Common Market Problems, 1963; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Conflict and Compromise in Belgian Politics, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Author: Val R. Lorwin
  - Item 7: Trade Union Education in the '70s, 1972; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Author: Pan-African Seminar on Trade Union Education Policy
  - Item 8: Collective Bargaining in Belgian Labour, 1969; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Author: Institut belge d'information et de documentation
  - Item 9: Statuten, 1960; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: Le Travail des Femmes dan sun Monde en Evolution, 1963; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 11: World Confederation of Labour, 1973; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Author: World Confederation of Labour
    Notes: Conference Program
  - Item 12: Centre for Productivity Study and Research, 1961; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Author: Rijksuniversiteit te Gent
  - Item 13: Trade Union Activities in the Field of Housing and Building, 1966; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Box: 4, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Bolivia: Portrait of a Retarded Country, 1952; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: Inter- American Regional Organization of Workers
  - Item 2: Hacia el Gobierno: Obrer - Campesino, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: Guillermo Lora
  - Item 3: Otra Experiencia en ;a 'politica de Aliados': Doctrina, 1962; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: Movimiento Nacionalista Revolucionario (Bolivia). Avanzada Universitaria
  - Item 4: The Economic Transformation of Bolivia, 1955; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: Carter Goodrich
  - Item 5: Hacia el Gobierno: Obrer - Campesino, 1962; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Programa Ideologico y Estatutos de la Central Obrera Boliviana, 1954; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: Central Obrera Boliviana
  - Item 7: Politica Agraria, 1952; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: Raul Solar Arancibia
  - Item 8: El Proceso Capitalista Occidental y la las Minas en Bolivia, 1952; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Author: Alipio Valencia Vega
  - Item 9: El Asalto Porista: El trotskismo y mineros de Bolivia, 1959; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Legislacion Agraria, 1953; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Ley General de Sociedades Cooperativas, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Educacion Sindical, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Box: 4, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Coimbra/Morris (exchange of labor agreements), 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Collegiate News and Views, 1957; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Slow Death in Bolivia, 1966; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Author: Norman Gall
  - Item 4: Clarin al Servicio de los Bolivianos n. 51, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Notes: newspaper
  - Item 5: El Diario (Several articles), 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Sobre La Revolucion Permanente, 1962; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Summary of the Labor Situation in Bolivia, 1958; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Author: United States. Bureau of Labor Statistics
  - Item 8: Rural Education in Bolivia, 1955; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Author: Institute of Inter- American Affairs (U.S.)
- Box: 4, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Discurso Informe del Secretario Ejecutivo, 1962; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Author: Juan Lechin Oquendo
  - Item 2: Estatutos y Reglamentos: Confederacion Sindicalde Bolivia, 1963; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Reglamentos y Estatutos: Relacion Historica - Sus Finalidades, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Cooperativas de Viviendas, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Guia Basica del Cooperativismo, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: El Cooperativismo y Sus Principios, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Historia Resumida Del Movimiento Sindical Internacional, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Reglamentos y Estatutos: Federacion Nacionalde Bolivia, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Economia Agraria Nacional, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Estatuto Organico de la Confederacion de TrabajadoresBolivia, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Estatutos de CONSBRA: El Dirigente debe actuarlos estatutos, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Sintesis del Contrato de Trabajo (Individual y Colectivo), 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: El Diario (Several articles), 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Presencia (Several Articles), 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Box: 4, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: A Report on Rural Syndicates in Pernambuco, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Author: Mary E. Wilkie
  - Item 2: A Report on Rural Syndicates in Pernambuco, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: A Report on Rural Syndicates in Pernambuco, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Brazil - Volta Redona Steel Works, 1960; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Brazil - Volta Redona Steel Works, 1959; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Evolution of Industrial Wages and Wage Policy in Brazil 1959-1967, 1968; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Author: Peter Gregory
  - Item 7: Brazil: An Economic Sketch, 1949; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Notes: map
- Box: 4, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Letter from Brazil, Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Second Pilot Plant Project: Brazil 11/18/62-2/9/63, 1963; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Author: Louis McAnly
  - Item 3: Report of Manning M. Exton: Brazil: 11/15/62-2/14/63, 1963; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Author: Manning M. Exton
  - Item 4: The Brazilian Law Student: Background, Habits, Attitudes, Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Theoria e Practica da Cooperacao, 1935; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Author: C.A. de Sarandy Raposo
  - Item 6: Problemas Brasileiros, 1967; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Estudos De Direito do Trabalho, 1961; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Author: Luis Ivani de Amorim Araujo
  - Item 8: Estatutos da Confederacao Nacional da Industria, 1954; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Confronto Entre Duas Pesquisas Sobre Lideranca Sindical, 1966; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Box: 4, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Communist Martyr Makers, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Author: British Guiana Trades Union Council
  - Item 2: The Communist Martyr Makers, 1964; Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Box: 4, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Electrical Union World{ Dupl entry}, 1960; Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Sugar Industry Labour Welfare Board, 1959; Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Notes: several articles
  - Item 3: Better Living, 1960; Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Annual Report, 1959; Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Electrical Union World, 1960; Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Notes: newspaper - 2 copies of same issue
  - Item 6: Sugar Worker, 1960; Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Box: 4, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Unemployment in Antigua, 1952; Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Author: Simon Rottenberg
  - Item 2: Social and Economic Studies, 1956; Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Author: University of the West Indies (Mona, Jamaica). Institute of Social and Economic Research
  - Item 3: The Economy of the West Indies, 1960; Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Author: George E. Cumper
  - Item 4: Report of a Board of Inquiry, 1955; Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Author: C. W. Burrows
  - Item 5: Labor and Nationalism in the British Caribbean, 1957; Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Author: George T. Daniel
  - Item 6: Canada and the Caribbean: Partners in Progress, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: The University College of the West Indies, Publication (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Author: T.W.J. Taylor
- Box: 4, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Loose Union Set for West Indies, 1961; Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Notes: news clipping
  - Item 2: Migration from West Indies Studied, 1960; Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: West Indies Boasts Own Top University, 1960; Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: West Indies Opens Conference Today, 1961; Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: West Indian Study Tour, 1960; Publication (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Box: 4, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: (title in Bulgarian alphabet), 1910; Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Notes: ?
  - Item 2: The General Workers Professional Union in Bulgaria, 1947; Publication (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Author: Bulgaria. Ministry of Information and Arts
- Box: 5, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Union-Management Co-operation at the Toronto FactoryLimited, 1947; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Le Mouvement ouvrier catholique au Canada: LettreCloutier, 1919; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Author: Omer Heroux
  - Item 3: A Brief History of Canadian Labor, 1956; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Author: Clifford A. Scotton
  - Item 4: The Shop Steward, 1957; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Author: Canadian Labour Congress. Education Dept.
  - Item 5: Organized Labour and Politics in Canada, 1971; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Author: Richard Ulric Miller
  - Item 6: Arbitration of Labor-Management Disputes in Canada, 1961; Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Author: Alton W. Craig
    Notes: article from Canadian Arbitration
  - Item 7: We Were There: Report of the Ten Canadian TradeUnion in 1951, Publication (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Author: Canadian-Soviet Friendship Society. National Council
- Box: 5, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Inflation and the Canadian Experience (New Publication notice), Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Reglement General (General By-Law), 1967; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Report on the Department of Labour, 1969; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Author: L.R. Peterson
  - Item 4: Labour Mobility, 1956; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Author: Trades and Labor Congress of Canada
  - Item 5: Canadian Independence and the People's Democracy, 1952; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Author: Communist Party of Canada. National Committee
  - Item 6: Government Policy on PricePeriod / Changes in Wage Control, 1946; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Author: William Lyon Mackenzie King
  - Item 7: What's Cookin'? A witch's brew or a national tonic, 1940; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Author: Workers' Educational Association
  - Item 8: The Lachine Strike of 1843, 1948; Publication (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Author: H.C. Pentland
    Notes: reprinted article
- Box: 5, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Correspondence - Coates, 1963; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Glossary (Canadian Labour Terms), 1964; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Canada's New Labor College, 1963; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Author: Max Swerdlow
  - Item 4: Organization Chart of the Canadian Labor CongressOrganizations, Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Notes: org. chart
  - Item 5: Service d'Education de la Confederation des TravailleursCanada, 1953; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Committee on Canadian Labour History Bulletin No. 1, Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Author: Committee on Canadian Labour History
  - Item 7: The Manpower Consultative Service, 1965; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Author: Canada. Dept. of Labour
  - Item 8: Industrial reconstruction and social development council, 1944; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Author: B.C. Shipyard Conference
  - Item 9: Canadian Labour History (No. 6 1975), Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Canadian Labour History (No. 7 1975), Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Workers' Educational Association Golden Jubilee, 1953; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Notes: conference program
  - Item 12: The Role of Trade Unions in the United Nations, Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Author: Kalmen Kaplansky
  - Item 13: Take the New Road: Peace, Trade, 100,000 New JobsPlatform, Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Notes: advertisement
  - Item 14: Handbook on Suggestion Plans, 1945; Publication (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Author: Labour- Management Production Committee
- Box: 5, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Canadian Industrial Relations - The Task Force Report, 1969; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Author: Adolf Sturmthal
  - Item 2: Committee on Canadian Labour History Bullten No. 1, 1976; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Notes: article - directory
  - Item 3: Hayes, James K. A., 1973; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Author: James K. A. Hayes
  - Item 4: The Montreal Policeman's Strike, 1970; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Author: Howard Goldblatt
  - Item 5: Correspondence - (Adams, Neufeld, Polisar and Isbester), 1965; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Canadian Labour History, 1974; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.4 (1974)
  - Item 7: Canadian Labour History, 1974; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.5 (1974)
  - Item 8: Canadian Labour History, 1973; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.2 (1973)
  - Item 9: Canadian Labour History, 1973; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.3 (1973)
  - Item 10: The Globe and Mail: Postmen Vote to Stay on Strike (and other articles), 1965; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: The Globe and Mail: Postal Workers Hold Out for Pledge of Arbitration (and other articles), 1965; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Seafarers Log: Statement of the Seafarers InternationalDisruption of Shipping, 1963; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: The New York Times magazine: What Happens When the Police Strike, 1969; Publication (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Box: 5, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Acuerdos Sindicales...en el Plano Presidencial (+ several articles), 1968; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Consejo Ejecutivo Nacional, 1965; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Consejo Ejecutivo Nacional, 1965; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Organic Structure of the Chilean Labor Movement: The Congresses, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Administrative Problems of Growth, 1958; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Author: Industrial Canada
  - Item 6: The Guaranteed Wage: A Panel Discussion, 1953; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Author: Montreal Board of Trade. Employee Relations Section
  - Item 7: Hourly Wages Rates Paid in the Printing IndustryMay 31st, 1954, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Author: Printing Industry Parity Committee for Montreal and District
  - Item 8: Hourly Wages Rates Paid in the Printing IndustryMay 31st, 1956, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Wage Rates, by Zones and by TradesMontreal and District, 1953; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Wage Rates, by Zones and by TradesMontreal and District, 1951; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Distribution of Employees According to Wage Rates Paid, 1956; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Family Allowances for Canada, 1944; Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Author: Dorothy H. Stepler
  - Item 13: Fortieth Anniversary 1908-1948, Publication (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Author: Canadian Brotherhood of Railway Employees and Other Transport Workers
- Box: 5, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Le Droit du Travail au Quebec, 1954; Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Author: Emile Bouvier
  - Item 2: Group: Hospital Services (supervisory and non-supervisory), 1972; Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Author: Canada. Treasury Board.
  - Item 3: Group: Historical Research (all employees), 1972; Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: The Maritime Labour Institute at Dalhousie University, 1945; Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Author: Maritime Labour Institute
  - Item 5: Le Salaire Annuel Garanti, 1953; Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: The Case for Union Security and the Check-Off, 1951; Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Author: Canadian Congress of Labour. Research Dept.
  - Item 7: An Historical Review: The Trade and Labor Congress of Canada, 1950; Publication (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Box: 5, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Caribbean Trade Unionist, 1959; Publication (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Author: Rawle Farley
- Box: 5, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Chapter 108: Employment of Women, Young Persons and Children, 1938; Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Chapter 108: Employment of Women, YoungChildren (revision), 1938; Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Chapter 111: Indian Immigrant Labour, 1938; Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Chapter 111: Indian Immigrant Labour (revision), 1938; Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Chapter 113: Tundus, 1938; Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Ordinance No. 13 of 1944: An Ordinance to amendOrdinance, Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Ordinance No. 16 of 1940: An Ordinance to giveundertakings, Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Ordinance No. 44 of 1942: An Ordinance to amendOrdinance, Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Ordinance No. 46 of 1941: An Ordinance to amendOrdinance, Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Ordinance No. 48 of 1939: An Ordinance to makepurposes, Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Ordinance No. 28 of 1939: An Ordinance to maketherewith, Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: Ordinance No. 8 of 1943: An Ordinance to amend theOrdinance, Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Item 13: Report on Labour Conditions in Ceylon, 1943; Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Author: Granville St. John Orde-Browne
  - Item 14: Industrial Disputes Ordinance, 1945; Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Item 15: Facts: Colombo Plan, 1963; Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Author: Colombo Plan Bureau
  - Item 16: May Day 1967, Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Author: Ceylon. Ministry of Labour, Employment and Housing
  - Item 17: May Day 1968, Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Item 18: May Day 1968, Publication (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Box: 5, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Chilean Labor: Struggle for Survival, 1975; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Author: AFL-CIO. Dept. of International Affairs
  - Item 2: ILO Governing Body asks Chile for Progress Report, 1975; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Author: ILO
  - Item 3: ILO Commission on Trade Union Situation in ChileReport, 1975; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: ILO Commission to Begin Three-Week Visitof Association, 1974; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Correspondence - (Neufeld/Wilam), 1973; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Amendment of Labor Code (translation), Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Notes: translations, Photo copy of a publ.
  - Item 7: The Chilean Labor Union Leader: A Preliminary ReportAttitudes, 1964; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Overseas Economic Surveys: Chile Economic and Commercial Conditions in Chile, 1958; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Author: J.H. Wright
  - Item 9: Cornell/Aid Project Contract Number ICAc - 1197 Final Report, 1966; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Author: New York State School of Industrial Relations
  - Item 10: Cornell/Aid ProjectFourth Report Covering Period 6/16/61-12/15/61, 1961; Publication (Box 5, Folder 9)
    Author: John P. Windmuller
- Box: 5, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Clasificacion de las Causales de las Huelgas Ilegales, Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Estadisticas Sindicales 1956-1972, Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Author: Universidad de Chile. Departamento de Relaciones del Trabajo y Desarrollo Organizacional
  - Item 3: Latin American Monographs: Genesis and Modernizationin Chile, 1961; Publication (Box 5, Folder 10)
    Author: Federico Guillermo Gil
- Box: 5, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Do Ideological Differences Have Personal Correlates?: ALevel, 1968; Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Analisis Critico del Derecho Colectivo del Trabajo, Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Author: William Thayer Arteaga
  - Item 3: Chile: Star in Ascent, 1962; Publication (Box 5, Folder 11)
    Author: Alexander S. Lipsett